And right up to the bay, the target burnt is
amazing, how many days is this trip because
this is a very good share, 1600 means
how much is it worth, you should come, the
destination is fixed, whenever you see such multi mantra 108 on chat, then the one who
goes there at all, he is in the box very soon,
so according to me, by
acting optimistically, various
targets should come, the international market is
going on, I will surprise you, then it comes soon
too, so according to the rate, adding
one month idea will be and we will reach
these levels after about 5-6 months of information,
hence the target practice WhatsApp message
along with the technical setup is telling
that here we can see good momentum above 14 years, so
absolutely, so see, now keep on noting, today
's high is 9943, which I am seeing
on one seat on the exchange and 1435 at 1440
is quite chewy, then hand 1440 is quite chewy
and this is very wonderful  And after that they
like this and this is very
true that you make money in share trading, if you do this then
you make money in the long term
and no
one can know this better than Ashish Chaturmohata, he has commented in this top box many times
and this so that the viewers
know that you must have it,
now I have liked it many times that if you have not
taken this then you have not taken anything, you are welcome,
tell me about the bus stop in insurance companies,
how do you feel about ICICI Lombard, GIC, so he was going to discuss
them, spirituality, Vidya Kunj Sharma
ji and your descendant ji, once
Sharma ji was going to discuss insurance
companies, he is very bullish on life and general
insurance, now like Rahul ji
targeted energy at 1600 and the lens you had mentioned,
but it was going to 1435, well there is
a resistance for the last several months, so
if it removes the supply that comes here, but then
I think 10 to 1657 can also be quite
possible, so from the general insurance
page, like its collection number  Those
who are interested in its solvency and who are
expecting in terms of market
share, just look at ICICI Lombard pick when the
bill goes perfectly, that thing's 1435 in
2014 Sharma ji's target is that after that I will do the
same on this and the target should be fixed
with Sharma ji, points 4800 grade but life
insurance SP should be
more than underworld
underpants pet and here also I think the
growth prospects that will come can be
treated in the next few years, so life
insurance Pepsi Life SBI Life
because of their product mix and their tune
with S Manya Jains which has started will continue
but this also seems to be a very attractive place,
they are showing very good work
and great performance, so this Technot Funda
Calls, now see Rahul Sharma ji will
like it, does he have any choice in marriage, Ashish
Chaturmohata ji crazy, I will ask him right now,
Ashish
Chaturmohata sir, has this been your favorite song at some point,
you also tell me your rent and your target
and see Ashish  Chaturmoha ji's
control is in front of you, the countdown of exactly 9 minutes 30
seconds has started, I
will tell you that trade 230, but
before that, do it from above,
I Yadav, we have always told you the same thing,
you just keep doing this and this and
HDFC Life is a long from True Horizon,
this strip, how should your portfolio be,
which Ghanshyam Pandey
will have in these stocks, technically definitely
1600, Sorabji said that it will definitely come,
but I think
you should send it on updates for trading only 25 to 30 percent,
Indian stocks should
remain in your portfolio, I am
fine, in the coming four-five years, at
least 16 utensils will be cleaned,
Cambodia will keep saying, so if I have any
other target in this, then I think if there is a 2
year fold, then
HDFC Life price came above ₹2000,
like before this, you can see the stop current level,
now I will talk about one more thing, this word, let
us emphasize the pattern of your
Industries  Loot Polio staff are
talking about them, then look at night, at any
price, around one and a half or you have
made good returns and see this,
we have already talked about all time gains and
after that both the Starks have shown a rise of 10 to 12
cents from there in just two days
that Akshara Consumer 1 - Let's see on your skin,
after consumer numbers, a little bit is for
Singh, but today
what an amazing Modia 470 6 store and let's talk,
but let's go to Ashish and
talk about color, exactly tomorrow about Bigg Boss,
what are some special numbers on which the market will be watching,
Ashish, tell me I will not delay you,
you eat hot air, I think you
know
that
when Katrina is not watching, thank you,
but this is the way of working while sitting at home,
no, old minute, tell me this, in your kitchen,
Chole Puri is made in Mumbai and
in Delhi, the fragrance of Bhavya Roop comes,
what is the connection, it is not a luck connection, is it a
matter that
it is just the opposite fragrance, positive
Chole Puri was not made here, okay, you guys
ICC officials were hearing that, it is a
strength based question in the chart, I have loose
that tomorrow is Friday, so the last
wedding day of the week and
you will see the results again, so tomorrow again know the
numbers of two companies that have appointed, apart from Cipla and Mahindra
& Mahindra's company RIM,
John
now Bata, India Container Corporation, Mahanagar
Gas, REC and Cement, all these changing
stocks, are they interesting to keep silent near this market, so for
you guys know the
numbers of Haridra Capital, Shimla Mirch, Amber Enterprises, Balrampur Sugar, BEML, Kajaria Ceramics, Punjab & Sindh Bank, Shipping Corporation, Shobha Sudarshan Chemical, Jeev's Smart Soya, the
list is long, I will
try to make it easy by breaking it up, M&M Financial
Services and Gateway District Park, the
rights entitlement etc. of both of these are
free and tomorrow is the last day of trading of Urs,
FD C Limited of both these companies,
tomorrow there is a board meeting, the board is going to consider Baba,
you might remember in Forbes
with Axis Bank's QIP  The TRP of these flats was
opened. The
issue price of QIP will be decided in the board meeting tomorrow.
CG Power has already started small companies.
They are almost neutral companies
but both of them have a board meeting tomorrow. The
boards of these companies are going to consider the special issue of work. Globally, the
personnel numbers of two special friends will be seen.
Yes's non-farm payroll and China
's import-export data. Both will be fed. Okay, that's fine,
Papa. So, the
focus is clearly on these. But one stock on which
you are focusing, look at it early in the morning. A
moment is coming. Show me the jackpot of Be Shabash.
Please give it a try. Jamuna and to
Jamuna Auto. Of course, these freight movements are
visible. Come out and further,
you had told me a lot of good fundamentals early in the morning, let's
revisit it once.
Disciple, I will give you all the birds. Did you tell
your father about some special hobby?
Because look, now
preparations are being made to build a second wave in it.
The sea is coming. And tell me why
you like Jamuna Auto today.
This stock is trading 10% higher in the market and I have
come to Master after seeing its volume
because you see today the volume in it is 10 crore
shares and
if I see the average volume then it is 1011 like shares
and in front of the volume of 10-11 like shares,
this is a whopping 1.25 crore shares and see this now
Sachin Bhai, I have made a mistake which is looking bad to you, if it looks bad
in this second year then
you will get a medical checkup because this will remove it,
you should tell this to the leaves a
little, father had chosen it,
after that you also go to my Ashish ji
and you